OBJECTIVE

I am actively pursuing a web developer position that offers exciting challenges and opportunities for innovation. My goal is to contribute to cutting-edge projects and deliver high-impact solutions that drive web experiences to new heights.

CONTACT

Isha0409isha@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/ishaisha0409

ishaisha04 (github.com)

07884241831

BIRMINGHAM, UK

EDUCATION

Front End Web Development Skills Bootcamp, funded by Department for Education, 2023 Training Provider OpenClassrooms

Post-Graduation 2021-2022 Master in Advance Computer Science (Msc. Computer Science) Birmingham City University (Birmingham)

SKILLS

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Github(version control)
- Experience with SASS Bootstrap and Tailwind CSS framework
- Fundamental knowledge of the React framework, PHP, SQL
- Familiarity with responsive web design principles and cross-browser compatibility and accessibility

SOFT SKILLS

- Strong problem-solving and troubleshooting abilities
- > Excellent attention to detail
- Effective communication and teamwork skills

Isha Isha

WEB DEVELOPER

Motivated professional with several years in customer service, transitioning to web development. Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Java Script, Bootstrap, CSS Tailwind, GitHub, WordPress, and WooCommerce. Committed to creating visually appealing websites for exceptional user experiences. I am open to relocation to the United Kingdom for the right opportunity.

EXPERIENCE

Volunteer Web Developer - East London Waterworks Park

Aug 20203-current

Actively participate in the organization's open-source projects on GitHub by collaborate with senior developers to select and resolve coding issues from a curated list. Applying coding and testing expertise to address identified issues, ensuring high-quality solutions.

Demonstrate proficiency in Git version control by pushing changes to GitHub repositories.

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT

Shell Petrol Station- Birmingham, England 04-2021-CURRENT Lakme Salon | Punjab, India 02-2018-02-2021

Projects

1. Booki Page:-

Developed a responsive tourism web page using HTML, CSS and achieved optimal user experience and browser compatibility across devices with responsive design techniques.

(https://ishaisha04.github.io/Booki1/)

2. OhMyFood Website (SASS and CSS Animations):

Designed captivating food website with 4 menu pages using SASS and CSS animations showing proficiency in CSS animation techniques and SASS. Ensured cross-device usability, browser compatibility, and version control using Git collaborative development.

(https://ishaisha04.github.io/ohmyfood/)

3. JavaScript Projects

Developed a calculator app and a todo list app using JavaScript to enhance user productivity and organization Integrated APIs for dynamic content, including dictionary, weather, random quotes, and joke generator. https://ishaisha04.github.io/Calculator/

https://ishaisha04.github.io/dictionary/

Some other HTML, CSS, JavaScript projects:-

https://ishaisha04.github.io/restaurant/| https://ishaisha04.github.io/portfolio/| https://ishaisha04.github.io/jokegenerator/